Previously on the show. Slowy fell sick.
上集說到，慢羊羊生病了
The stars initially thought that Wolffy and the goats made him sick.
星星們認為狼羊 就是讓寶寶生病的元兇
The goats insisted on helping, which finally got Slowy better.
在小羊的再三堅持下 終於讓慢羊羊的病情好轉
The stars have also come to accept Wolffy and the goats.
星星們也接納了狼羊
But how can they make Slowy go back to the way he used to be?
但怎樣才能讓慢羊羊恢復原樣呢？
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: The Invincible Baby"
《奇幻天空島之》
So you ate the fruit from the tree and became small?
原來村長是吃了樹上的果子變小的呀
Those are infantilising fruits.
那些是幼稚果
They make people young again.
會讓人返老還童
Baby, it's time to eat.
寶寶該吃飯囉
I made something delicious for you.
我給你準備了美味的食物
I can't drink from a milk bottle in front of the children. That's too embarrassing.
在孩子面前用奶瓶喝奶，太丟臉了
Grandpa Elder. The chief is actually an adult, not a baby.
長老爺爺，我們村長其實是大人 不是小寶寶
He became a baby after eating one of those infantilizing fruits.
只是吃了幼稚果才變小的
You keep saying he's an adult. How old is he?
你們老說他是大人 那他年紀有多大呀？
He's in his 80s.
八十多歲了
That's still very young. I'm more than 2,000 years old.
那還很小嘛，我都兩千多歲了
Come, drink some milk.
來，喝奶吧
How can we turn Chief back to what he used to be?
到底要怎樣才能把村長變回原樣呢？
You can look for Time Star.
可以找“時光星”啊
Who is that?
時光星是誰？
He's the most famous performance judge in the sky.
他是天上最著名的“表演星評員”
If he gives a performance five stars, everyone will eagerly come to see it.
只要被他評上五星的演出 大家都會蜂擁而來
But what does that have to do with Chief?
但是，這跟村長恢復原樣 有什麼關係呢？
That's because his superpower is to make people old.
因為他的能力是讓人變老
How can we find him?
那怎樣才能找到他？
He's always alone. It's hard to find him.
他獨來獨往，很難找到他的
But...
不過…
But what?
不過什麼？
If our troupe manages to get 10,000 likes,
不過只要我們劇場集齊一萬個讚
he'll definitely come.
他就會被吸引過來了
Great! What does he look like?
太好了！那時光星長什麼樣子呀？
Um, I think there's a photo of him in Handsome Star's place.
我記得在變帥星家裡好像有他的照片
Who's that? Can he make me handsome?
變帥星又是誰？他能讓我變帥嗎？
No.
不能
That's because his superpower is to make himself handsome when no one's around.
因為他的能力 是讓自己在沒有人的時候變帥
What can I do to those stars so I can catch Slowy?
怎樣才能對付那群老星星 趁機抓住慢羊羊呢？
Pay.
給錢
That's too simple.
膚淺
I'm asking you to pay now!
我是叫你給錢結帳！
Okay.
好
Go next door and get me some facial masks. I'm going to buy shoes.
等一下你去隔壁那裡幫我買面膜 我要去買鞋子
Okay.
好
There are so many people buying masks.
這麼多居民買面膜啊
Grandpa.
爺爺
Who did you call grandpa?
誰是爺爺？
Have you ever seen such a fit grandpa?
有看過這麼健壯的爺爺嗎？
Are you not a grandpa?
您不是爺爺？
Then what are you doing at the senior activity center?
那您為什麼要來康樂中心啊？
What? Senior activity center?
什麼，康樂中心？
Oh, dear. I came to the wrong place.
糟糕，來錯地方了
Senior activity center?
康樂中心？
So old people love senior activity centers.
原來老人們都超愛康樂中心
What if I open one?
假如我也開一家的話
The stars will be at the center all the time.
星星們就會只顧著去康樂中心玩
Then I'll have lots of time to get the goats.
我就有大把的時間去抓羊了
That's a great idea.
這主意真不錯
Where are my masks?
我的面膜呢？
How handsome you are.
真是英俊啊
Grandpa Handsome Star.
變帥星爺爺
Who's that?
誰？
Sorry to disturb you, Grandpa Handsome Star.
打擾了，變帥星爺爺
We need your help.
我們想請您幫忙
This is the photo of Time Star. Here you go.
這就是時光星的照片，給您
Handsome Star, let's go out and have some fun.
變帥星，一起去玩吧
The picture of grandpa Time Star flew away.
時光星爺爺的照片飛走了
Thank you.
謝謝
Today is the official opening of Wolffy's senior activity center!
今天，灰太狼的康樂中心正式開業了
Come. Come inside.
來…都進來吧
Dear friends,
各位朋友
this is Wolffy's senior activity center.
請看灰太狼康樂中心
Look at the layout.
這樣的擺設
Look at the facilities. It's so...
這樣的設施，實在太…
Isn't it amazing?
是不是太棒了？
It's mediocre.
太一般了
But since you just opened, we'll come to visit.
不過你才開業，我們肯定來捧場
Thank you.
還是謝謝你們
I need to think of a way to get Slowy.
得想個辦法把慢羊羊弄到手才行
By the way, is the baby still feeling unwell?
對了，寶寶還有沒有不舒服呢？
Shall I give him a check-up?
要不要我幫他檢查一下呢？
Well...
這…
We don't want him to get sick again.
萬一寶寶再生病就麻煩了
I'll let you have him then.
寶寶就拜託你了
Sure.
好
The little goat has a mark. You must have one too.
小羊有印記，你肯定也有
There it is.
果然有
Is the baby okay?
寶寶沒事吧？
I haven't examined him yet.
還沒檢查呢
I'm not used to having someone looking when I'm examining people.
我不習慣有人看著我檢查的
It's okay, I'm not looking at you.
沒關係，我不是看你
I'm looking at the baby.
我是看寶寶
But you will distract me.
可是你會影響到我的
I'll leave then.
那我出去吧
Is the baby okay?
寶寶沒事吧？
He's okay.
沒事…
If he's okay, I'll take him then.
沒事的話，我就把他抱出去了
No. He's not okay.
不對，有事…
What did you say?
你說什麼？
I'm sorry.
對不起
When I get anxious, my superpower gets out of control.
我緊張的時候，技能會失控
What's wrong with the baby?
寶寶出什麼事了？
I mean, he needs some rest.
我的意思是，寶寶需要好好休息啊
Stop holding him everywhere you go.
你就不要抱來抱去的了
What should I do with my hair?
我的毛怎麼辦啊？
Let me help you. Shorter hair!
讓我來幫你吧，頭髮變短！
My hair!
我的頭髮啊！
Why do you guys keep coming over?
你們老是過來幹什麼？
I was afraid the baby might be bored when he wakes up.
我怕寶寶醒了會無聊嘛
I'll be there when he wakes up. Just go and have fun.
他醒了我會陪他的，你們放心去玩吧
All right.
好吧
Let me help you!
我幫你們！
Sorry. My aura is just too strong.
對不起，都怪我的氣場太厲害了
The photo is dirty now.
照片髒了
I'm sorry.
對不起
If I hadn't asked Handsome Star to go to Wolffy's senior activity center,
如果不是我找變帥星 去灰太狼開的康樂中心玩
the photo wouldn't have flown away and it wouldn't have gotten dirty.
照片就不會飛走了，也不會髒了
Wolffy has a senior activity center?
灰太狼開了一家康樂中心？
Yes. Elder Star and the baby are there now.
對呀，長老星和寶寶都去了
You old goat.
老羊
Stop struggling.
別作無謂的掙扎了
Don't run!
別跑！
The baby won!
寶寶贏了！
Help!
救命啊！
The baby is amazing.
寶寶真棒
Seeing you play makes me want to play badminton too.
看完你打球 我突然想來一場羽毛球賽
Me too. Baby, be good.
我也是，寶寶乖
Play with Uncle Wolffy.
跟灰太狼叔叔玩
Yes, give him to me.
對，把寶寶交給我就好了
I won't let you off.
我不會放過你的
Help!
救命啊！
Baby, hush now, or I'll lose.
寶寶別鬧，再鬧我就輸了
Come on, baby. Play with me over here. Don't get in their way.
來，寶寶，我帶你去那邊玩 別打擾長老星
Yes. This'll make me win.
對啊，走這一步就贏了
Baby, you're awesome.
寶寶你真棒
Baby, can you play chess?
寶寶，你會下棋？
He can play badminton too.
他還會打羽毛球呢
That's not all. He got a perfect score bowling.
不僅這樣，打保齡球還滿分呢
Wow! You're really an invincible baby.
想不到你真是個無敵小寶寶
All of you guys underestimate me. Ah!
老狼不發威，你當我是汪汪
I thought I saw something fly out.
剛才好像有什麼飛出去了
Chief is all right! That's great.
村長沒事，太好了！
We just need to clean the photo.
照片擦一擦就好了
Chief. We'll find Time Star and get you back to normal.
村長，我們一定會把時光星找回來 讓你恢復正常的
I guess Chief is going to have to drink milk again.
看來村長又會被抱去喝奶了
Baby, we really underestimated you.
寶寶，之前我們實在是太小看你了
You're amazing.
沒想到你那麼厲害
My heart tells me I want to play chess.
我的心告訴我想下棋
Come play with me.
寶寶陪我下吧
I'll do anything to avoid drinking milk.
只要不喝奶，什麼都行
But before that, you have to drink your milk.
但下棋前，還是要喝奶的
TO BE CONTINUED 0004 DAYS FROM SETTING SAIL
（未完待續 距離啟航還剩4天）